[
  {
    "question": "What house does Harry belong to?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Slytherin",
      "Hufflepuff",
      "Ravenclaw"
    ],
    "correct": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What position does Harry play on his Quidditch team?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Chaser",
      "Keeper",
      "Auror"
    ],
    "correct": "Seeker"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Crookshanks?",
    "incorrect": [
      "A troll",
      "Harry's love interest",
      "A three-headed dog"
    ],
    "correct": "Hermione's cat"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is the Summoning Charm?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Expecto Patronum",
      "Wingardium Leviosa",
      "Avada Kedavra"
    ],
    "correct": "Accio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of dragon did Harry face in the first Tri-Wizard Tournament task?",
    "incorrect": [
      "A Norwegian Ridgeback",
      "A Chinese Fireball",
      "A Common Welsh Green"
    ],
    "correct": "A Hungarian Horntail"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who dies in the third Tri-Wizard Tournament task?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Hagrid",
      "Viktor Krum",
      "Fleur Delacour"
    ],
    "correct": "Cedric Diggory"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Thestral?",
    "incorrect": [
      "A house elf",
      "A fairy",
      "A death eater"
    ],
    "correct": "An invisible winged horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Harry catch his first snitch?",
    "incorrect": [
      "With his hands",
      "With a net",
      "He coaxes it to him"
    ],
    "correct": "With his mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are Hogwarts Students placed in their houses?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Professor Dumbledore assigns them",
      "They are sorted by height",
      "They have to fight it out"
    ],
    "correct": "The Sorting Hat decides"
  },
  {
    "question": "What talent does Harry share with Voldemort?",
    "incorrect": [
      "He can recite the wizard alphabet backwards",
      "He's an Auror",
      "He's an Animagus"
    ],
    "correct": "He's a Parselmouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Moaning Myrtle die?",
    "incorrect": [
      "The Whomping Willow whomped her",
      "A Nosebleed Nougat",
      "From apparating"
    ],
    "correct": "The Basilisk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Felix Felicis do?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Makes hair grow on your face",
      "Makes you float",
      "Poisons you"
    ],
    "correct": "Gives good luck"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who does Harry see in the mirror shard?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Sirius Black",
      "His parents",
      "Dobby"
    ],
    "correct": "Aberforth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the half-blood prince?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Draco Malfoy",
      "Remus Lupin",
      "Peeves"
    ],
    "correct": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dumbledore buried with?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Fawkes",
      "The Resurrection Stone",
      "The Sword of Gryffindor"
    ],
    "correct": "The Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Rita Skeeter slip around Hogwarts undetected to spy and obtain gossip for her articles?",
    "incorrect": [
      "She uses the Marauder's Map",
      "She uses an invisibility cloak",
      "She uses an extendable ear"
    ],
    "correct": "She's an unregistered animagus and can turn into a beetle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does a Dementor do?",
    "incorrect": [
      "They collect brooms",
      "They make a person go crazy",
      "They play pranks"
    ],
    "correct": "They suck out a person's soul with the Dementors' Kiss"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Horace Slughorn disguise himself as when Dumbledore and Harry first visit?",
    "incorrect": [
      "An elf",
      "A tree",
      "A portrait"
    ],
    "correct": "An armchair"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the Marauder's Map show?",
    "incorrect": [
      "The way to the Chamber of Secrets",
      "Directions to the Marauder's house",
      "The Room of Requirement"
    ],
    "correct": "The location of everyone at Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Harry's Patronus?",
    "incorrect": [
      "An owl",
      "A horse",
      "A wolf"
    ],
    "correct": "A stag"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not a method of transport for wizards?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Apparition",
      "A portkey",
      "Floo Powder"
    ],
    "correct": "Abracadabra"
  }
]